var data = [
  {
    "category": "Quotes",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is _______________",
        "answer": "To get permission"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "You manage ________, you lead _________",
        "answer": "You manage <i>things</i>, you lead <i>people</i>"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "Humans are allergic to _________",
        "answer": "Change"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "If it's a good idea, _______________________",
        "answer": "Go ahead and do it"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Career",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What was Grace Hopper's highest naval rank?",
        "answer": "Rear admiral"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "What computer did Grace Hopper first work on?",
        "answer": "Harvard Mark I"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "Which language that Grace Hopper worked on is the most widely-used?",
        "answer": "COBOL"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "What was the name of Grace Hopper's first compiler work?",
        "answer": "The A compiler"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Programming",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What is it called to remove a moth stuck in a relay?",
        "answer": "Debugging"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "What does the acronym COBOL stand for?",
        "answer": "COmmon Business-Oriented Language"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "How long is a nanosecond in wire?",
        "answer": "11.8 inches (30 cm)"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "What does an all-capitalized word signify in COBOL?",
        "answer": "Reserved word"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Conference",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What city is hosting GHC 2018?",
        "answer": "Houston, Texas"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "How many people attended GHC 2017?",
        "answer": "18,000"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "Who founded the Grace Hopper Celebration?",
        "answer": "Dr. Anita Borg and Dr. Telle Whitney"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "When was the Grace Hopper Celebration founded?",
        "answer": "1994"
      }
    ]
  }
];
